[
    {   "question"  : "C'est pas faux.",
        "answer"    : "Kaamelott",
        "category"  : 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "T'es tendue Natacha.",
        "answer"    : "Dikkenek",
        "category"  : 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Salut à tous les gamers, c'est ...",
        "answer"    : "WaRTeK",
        "category"  : 4,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "I'm the one who knocks",
        "answer"    : "Breaking Bad",
        "category"  : 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Vous savez, moi je ne crois pas qu'il y ait de bonne ou de mauvaise situation.",
        "answer"    : "Astérix et Obélix : Mission Cléopâtre",
        "category"  : 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "C'est trop calme... j'aime pas trop beaucoup ça... J'préfère quand c'est un peu trop plus moins calme...",
        "answer"    : "Astérix et Obélix : Mission Cléopâtre",
        "category"  : 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Le mec... Il s'appelle On ! Donc c'est le phare-à-On ! Le pharaon !",
        "answer"    : "Astérix et Obélix : Mission Cléopâtre",
        "category"  : 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Le lion ne s'associe pas avec le cafard.",
        "answer"    : "Astérix et Obélix : Mission Cléopâtre",
        "category"  : 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Il est bizarre ce sol, il est pas palpable...",
        "answer"    : "Astérix et Obélix : Mission Cléopâtre",
        "category"  : 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "The cake is a lie.",
        "answer"    : "Portal",
        "category"  : 7,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Conformément au protocole de test, nous arrêterons de vous mentir dans 3, 2 ,1.. *brouillage*",
        "answer"    : "Portal",
        "category"  : 7,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Bonjour et bienvenue au centre d'enrichissement assisté par ordinateur d'Aperture Science.",
        "answer"    : "Portal",
        "category"  : 7,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Incroyable ! {Nom du sujet}, vous devez faire la fierté de {Ville du sujet}.",
        "answer"    : "Portal",
        "category"  : 7,
        "difficulty": 3,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Conformément au protocole de test déjà cité, nous ne pouvons plus vous mentir.",
        "answer"    : "Portal",
        "category"  : 7,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Just Do It.",
        "answer"    : "Nike",
        "category"  : 3,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "I'm Lovin' It",
        "answer"    : "McDonald's",
        "category"  : 3,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Broadcast yourself",
        "answer"    : "YouTube",
        "category"  : 3,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "L'encyclopédie libre",
        "answer"    : "Wikipédia",
        "category"  : 3,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Notre passion, votre formation",
        "answer"    : "CPLN",
        "category"  : 3,
        "difficulty": 3,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "C'est gratuit, mais ça ne le restera pas toujours",
        "answer"    : "Facebook",
        "category"  : 3,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Don't be evil",
        "answer"    : "Google",
        "category"  : 3,
        "difficulty": 3,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Baisez-vous vous-mêmes, Parce que, moi, j'ai plus l'droit d'vous ken",
        "answer"    : "Orelsan",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Basique, simple, simple, basique ",
        "answer"    : "Orelsan",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Show me your moves",
        "answer"    : "Captain Falcon",
        "category"  : 6,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Il n'y a qu'une seule vérité!",
        "answer"    : "Détective Conan",
        "category"  : 2,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Non ce n'était pas le radeau de la méduse, ce bateau",
        "answer"    : "Georges Brassens",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 3,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "J'avais envie de dire bonjour à n'importe qui ",
        "answer"    : "Joe Dassin",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "The faster we're falling, We're stopping and stalling, We're running in circles again",
        "answer"    : "Sum 41",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Firstborn unicorn, Hardcore soft porn",
        "answer"    : "Red Hot Chili Peppers",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Can't stop, addicted to the shindig, Chop Top, he says I'm gonna win big",
        "answer"    : "Red Hot Chili Peppers",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "I just wanna stay in the sun where I find, I know it's hard sometimes",
        "answer"    : "Twenty One Pilots",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Taking my time on my ride",
        "answer"    : "Twenty One Pilots",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "I can't believe how much I hate, Pressures of a new place roll my way",
        "answer"    : "Twenty One Pilots",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Is there anyone out there 'cause it's getting harder and harder to breathe",
        "answer"    : "Maroon 5",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Moi je n'étais rien et voilà qu'aujourd'hui, je suis le gardien...",
        "answer"    : "Francis Cabrel",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Je garde les pieds sur terre, Je garde la tête froide",
        "answer"    : "Francis Cabrel",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "There's a lady who's sure, All that glitters is gold",
        "answer"    : "Stairway to Heaven",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Come as you are, as you were",
        "answer"    : "Nirvana",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Take your time, hurry up, The choice is yours, don't be late",
        "answer"    : "Nirvana",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Memoria, memoria, Memoria, memoria",
        "answer"    : "Nirvana",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 3,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Load up on guns, bring your friends, It's fun to lose and to pretend",
        "answer"    : "Nirvana",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "I'm so happy 'cause today, I've found my friends",
        "answer"    : "Nirvana",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Polly wants a cracker, Maybe she would like some food",
        "answer"    : "Nirvana",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "And all the girls say I'm pretty fly (for a white guy)",
        "answer"    : "The Offspring",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Mark still lives at home cause he's got no job, He just plays guitar and smokes a lot of pot",
        "answer"    : "The Offspring",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 3,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "I never knew you were the someone waiting for me",
        "answer"    : "Ed Sheeran",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "The club isn't the best place to find a lover, So the bar is where I go",
        "answer"    : "Ed Sheeran",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Oh baby, don't you know I suffer? Oh baby, can you hear me moan?",
        "answer"    : "Muse",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Is this the real life? Is this just fantasy?",
        "answer"    : "Queen",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Shook me all night long, Yeah you shook me all night long",
        "answer"    : "AC/DC",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "When you die, I'll be the one writing your name in my Death Note.",
        "answer"    : "Death Note",
        "category"  : 2,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "The human whose name is written in this note shall die.",
        "answer"    : "Death Note",
        "category"  : 2,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Yuki Yuki Yuki",
        "answer"    : "Mirai Nikki",
        "category"  : 2,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Tu~tu~ruuu...mayushii-desu",
        "answer"    : "Steins:Gate",
        "category"  : 2,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Imagination is more important than knowledge.",
        "answer"    : "Albert Einstein",
        "category"  : 6,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "I'd rather be hated for who I am, than loved for who I am not.",
        "answer"    : "Kurt Cobain",
        "category"  : 6,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "That's one small step for a man, one giant leap for mankind.",
        "answer"    : "Neil Armstrong",
        "category"  : 6,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Hakuna matata",
        "answer"    : "Le Roi Lion",
        "category"  : 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "When you were here before Couldn't look you in the eye",
        "answer"    : "Radiohead",
        "category"  : 5,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Une maquette ?! Vous avez pas dit qu'c'était une catapulte ?",
        "answer"    : "Kaamelott",
        "category"  : 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "À ROULEEEEETTES !! HOULA... J'l'ai un peu trop gueulé ça, non ? À roulettes.",
        "answer"    : "Kaamelott",
        "category"  : 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "13, 14, 15... Enfin tous les chiffres impairs jusqu'à 22.",
        "answer"    : "Kaamelott",
        "category"  : 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Sire, Sire ! On en a gros !",
        "answer"    : "Kaamelott",
        "category"  : 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Faut arrêter ces conneries de nord et de sud ! Une fois pour toutes, le nord, suivant comment on est tourné, ça change tout !",
        "answer"    : "Kaamelott",
        "category"  : 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "media_type": 0
    },
    {   "question"  : "Pas de pierre, pas de palais. Pas de palais, ... pas de palais.",
        "answer"    : "Astérix et Obélix : Mission Cléopatre",
        "category"  : 4,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "media_type": 0
    }
]